A Finding Aid to the Exhibition Records of the Contemporary Study Wing of the Finch College Museum of Art, 1943-1975, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1943-1975; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 14.9 Linear feet Boxes 6-22, OV 24-25, FC 26
  - "Documentation" (1968), Archival Resource Key (Box 13)
    - Catalog Drafts and Galleys, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Catalog Drafts, Galleys, and Final Catalog, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Catalog Mechanicals, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Catalog Photographs, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Labels for Vitrines, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Letters and Photographs Exhibited, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Loan Forms, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Loan Forms, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Photographs, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Press Release, Announcement and Clipping, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Research, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 31)
      Oversized clipping in box 22, folder 4.
  - "The Dominant Woman" (1968-1969), Archival Resource Key (Box 13)
    - Article by M. Citron and J. Gelb, "Venus Through the Ages", circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Biographies, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 33)
      Oversized item in box 22, folder 5.
    - Catalog, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Catalog Drafts and Galleys, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 35)
      Oversized galleys in box 22, folder 5.
    - Catalog Photographs, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Clippings, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 37)
      Oversized clipping in box 22, folder 5.
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 38)
      See also under research for additional correspondence with prospective artists for the exhibition.
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Lists, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Loan Forms, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Loan Forms, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Photographs of Artists, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Photographs of Artwork, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Photographs of Opening, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Receipts and Deliveries, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Research, Correspondence and Photographs, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Research, Correspondence and Photographs, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Research, Correspondence and Photographs, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 51)
      Oversized clipping housed in box 22, folder 5.
    - Research, Notes and Writings, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Research, Printed Material, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 53)
      Oversized posters in OV 23, folder 13.
  - "Drawings by New York Artists" (not realized at Finch College), 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - "Ellsworth Kelly" (not realized), 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - "Energy Sculpture" (1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Catalog Text, Final Catalog, and Biographies, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Oversized clippings housed in box 22, folder 5.
    - Correspondence, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - "Finch College Alumnae and Their Husbands" (1969), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Lists and Writings, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets of Opening and Installation, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - "Five Centuries of Graphic Art" (1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Catalog, Announcement, and Press Release, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Catalog and Announcement Drafts, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1066; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Lists and Receipts, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Loan Agreement Forms, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Loan Agreement Forms, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Loan Agreement Forms, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Loan Agreement Forms, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - "Les Formes Vivantes: Alexander Archipenko" (1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Oversized catalog draft housed in OV 25.
  - "Forms in Metal" (1975), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Bills, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Catalog, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Installation, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Insurance, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Loan Forms and Correspondence, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Loan Forms and Correspondence, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Loan Forms and Correspondence, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Loan Forms and Correspondence, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Notes and Writings, circa 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Photographs of Artwork, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Press Releases and Clippings, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 34)
      Oversized clippings in box 22, folder 5.
    - Research, 1943-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - "Four Contemporary African Artists" (not realized), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - General File, 1962-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - General File, 1962-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - General Files, 1962-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Bank Presentation, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - "French Landscape Painters from Four Centuries" (1965-1966), Checklist, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - "Galaxy of Ladies: American Paintings from the Paul Magriel Collection" (1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Catalog, Press Release, Announcement, and Clippings, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Paul Magriel Correspondence, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Photographs of Artwork, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - "Giacometti: The Complete Graphics" (1971), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Checklist, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence and Contracts, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Photographs and Catalog Correspondence, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Press Releases and Clippings, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - "Grafica Oggi: Contemporary Graphics from the Studio 2RC in Rome" (1974), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Catalog, Press Release and Clippings, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Insurance, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Notes and Photograph, circa 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - "Guerrero Stone Sculpture" (1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Catalog Checklist, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Catalog Drafts, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Loan Correspondence, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Loan Forms, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Loan Forms, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Loan Valuation, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Press Releases, Announcements, and Clippings, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Receipts, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - "Hans Richter Retrospective" (1968), Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Announcement, Guest List, and Attendance Statistics, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Catalog and Price List, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Clippings and Reviews, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, General, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Hans Richter, 1967-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Film Program, 1947, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Interview with Hans Richter, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Lists of Artworks, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Loan Forms, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Photographs for Catalog, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Photographs for Catalog, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Photographs for Catalog, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified Sketch, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 15)
      Oversized sketch in box 22, folder 5.
    - Writings, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - "Homenatge a Joan Prat, by Joan Miro" (1972), Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, Insurance, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Printed Materials, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - "Hugo Weber: A Retrospective Exhibition" (1975), Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Catalog, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Catalog Drafts, Notes, and Receipts, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, General, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Embassy of Switzerland, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Embassy of Switzerland, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Lenders, circa 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1972-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1972-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Photographs of Weber, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Research, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key; Includes one sound cassette (Box 15, Folder 29)
      Contains a transcript and sound recoridng of an interview with Ruth Richards.
    - Swiss Society Party, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - "Images of an Era" (not realized), 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - "Irish Directions" (not realized), 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - "Italian Visual Poetry" (1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Catalog, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence and Loan Documentation, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence and Loan Documentation, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Insurance Valuation, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Lists and Notes, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 37)
      Oversized list in OV 25.
    - Photographs of Installation, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Press Release, Announcement, and Clippings, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Printed Material, 1973 and undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Proposal, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - "Jack Sonenberg" (not realized), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - "Jacques Kaplan's Private Collection" (1969), Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Catalog Drafts, Galleys, and Final Catalog, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 43)
      Oversized galleys housed in OV 25.
    - Letters and Receipts, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Lists, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Loan Forms, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Loan Forms, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Photographs, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Press Release and Clippings, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 49)
      Oversized clipping in Box 22, folder 5.
  - "James Brooks Retrospective" (1975), Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Catalog Drafts, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 52)
      See also research file for additional correspondence with Brooks.
    - Correspondence, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Press Release, Announcement, and Clippings, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Research, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Research, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Interview with Brooks and Janet Katz, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 58)
      Transcript only.
  - "Jan Cybis" (1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 16)
    - Catalog, Press Release, Announcement, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Kazimir Gallery Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 16)
      - Jan Cybis, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Henryk Stazewski, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Jean Gorin, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Notes and Writings, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Photographs for Catalog, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Photograph of Cybis and Warsaw Installation, 1959, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Receipts, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - "Josephine and Philip Bruno Collection" (1965-1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 16)
    - Catalog, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Clippings, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence and Loan Forms, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence and Loan Forms, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Lists, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Photographs of Installation Views, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - "Lila Katzen: Rolled Steel Sculpture" (not realized), 1974-1975; 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - "N-Dimensional Space" (1970), Archival Resource Key (Box 16)
    - Artist's Submission from Joel Stein, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 29)
      Oversized schematic drawings in OV 25.
    - Catalog, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Clippings, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 31)
      Oversized clippings in OV 25
    - Correspondence, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence with Laser Lenders, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Discussion of Holography, 1970; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 16, Folder 36)
      With Lloyd G. Cross, Allyn Z. Lite, and Gerald Thomas Bern Pethick
    - Interview with Margaret Benyon, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Loan Forms, Receipts, and Insurance, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Photographs, Negatives and Contact Sheets, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Photographs, Prints and Transparencies, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 40)
      Oversized photographs in box 22, folder 6
    - Press Release and Publicity, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Proposals and Budget, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Research, circa 1965-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Technical Specifications and Floor Plans, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Traveling Exhibition, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Traveling Exhibition, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Unidentified Sketches, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 47)
      Possibly by G. Pethick
  - "New Materials, Impossible Art" (not realized), circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - "New Materials, Impossible Art" (not realized), circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - "Patrick Ireland: 10 Years" (not realized), 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Philip Pearlstein (1974), Archival Resource Key (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Insurance, Shipping, and Receipts, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Insurance Claim, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - "Philip Pearlstein" (1974), Archival Resource Key (Box 17)
    - Lists, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Loan Forms, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Press Release, Publicity, and Clippings, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - "Posters by Artists" (1969), Archival Resource Key (Box 17)
    - Clippings, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Condition Reports, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Lists, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Lists, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Lists, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Notes and Writings, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Photographs, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Posters, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Oversized poster in box 22, folder 6
  - "Prints from Hollanders Workshop" (1972), Archival Resource Key (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Interview with Irwin Hollander, 1972 February 17; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Lists, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Photographs, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Press Release and Clippings, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - "The Private Collection of Martha Jackson" (1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 17)
    - 15th Anniversary Celebration 1953-1968, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Condition Reports and Catalog, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Interview with David Anderson, Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette Includes transcript (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Lists, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Press Release, Announcement, and Clippings, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Theft of Arman Collage, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - "Projected Art" (1966-1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 17)
    - Artist Biographies, circa 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 17)
      - Alexander Alexieff, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Maurice Amar, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Kenneth Anger, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Bruce Baille, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Paul Bartel, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Ilya Bolotowsky, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - Stan Brakhage, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Robert Breer, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - David Brooks, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 39)
      - Peter Campus, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - Bruce Connor, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - James Davis, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - Carmen D'Avino, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - Ed Emshwiller, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 44)
      - Jules Engel, 1964-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 45)
        Oversized poster in box 22, folder 6.